Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The names of those who had passed the Royal Knights selection exam were finally announced.
Zora, who'd also passed, was late to the ceremony.
With the inclusion of three additional members, Shiren Tiam, Cobb Portaport, and Nozel Silva, Captain of the Silver Eagles,
the ranks of the Royal Knights would now boast a total of 20 elite warriors.
Victory is all we need! The Eye of the Midnight Sun is a contemptible terrorist organization!
If we don't pull it up by the roots ourselves, our nation will never know peace!
Rest assured we will be making our way to their base immediately!
Listen up! It lies in the floating dungeon found within the strong magic region called Gravitostones!
!
It taks what it's like
But Anton Schmidt
Why don't you say he's in real character?
What is it?
But let's pretend to die
It has been there
I delle so much
Action.
Oh no, we all have legal skills.
You may each see a very dark style such as time to and then pass it over.
To be continued...
So, um...
How's Foygolion doing?
He's still unconscious.
After the capital was attacked, he was abducted.
They must have done something to him, but we never figured out what it was.
Whatever it is, it's bad.
Though, if he were conscious, I know exactly how he'd react.
He'd say, I failed to overpower my opponent because I'm lacking experience.
Either way, it's not the end for me.
I'll train harder and surpass you both.
Watch me!
Wow, Leopold.
I'll get revenge for Captain Foygolion.
Don't worry about that.
Unlike most people, he didn't laugh at my dream of becoming the next Wizard King.
He even called me a rival.
I am who I am now, because Captain Foygolion believed in me.
And so am I.
There isn't any shame in being weak, girl.
The shame is in staying weak.
What he said helped me to grow stronger.
Asta!
Noelle!
I'm counting on you.
Trust me.
We're gonna bring peace to the Clover Kingdom.
By stopping the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
We gotta fight together soon, too, Leo.
You're on, pal.
Careful, Alfin.
Right.
We'll be back.
So Captain Foygolion and Finral are both unconscious now.
I hope they wake up before too much longer.
Actually, the way that Mana felt before, it might have had something to do with the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
We've got to defeat them fast.
You're right.
But you know, there's something that's been bugging me for a long time now.
Well, back when I was fighting that big hairy guy, he said they'd never forgive us.
That we're fighting because we have a grudge.
So, does that mean if we forgave each other, we wouldn't have to fight?
But who is we?
I don't know!
It feels like the more I talk about this, the more I confuse myself!
That's because you're an idiot who's trying to be deep.
I'm not an idiot!
I ain't come to think of it, Captain Yami said the exact same thing!
Okay, I'll clear my head with some strength training!
Crunches!
And I gotta do a few back extensions, too!
You stupid brute.
So many crabs!
Unbelievable.
Oh, look!
You know, Mimosa and Specs are here.
Did all of you come here to visit Captain Foygolion, too?
No, I'm afraid not.
You see, among all the magic nightroids...
Asta! Are you all right?
The golden dawn...
Yep, don't worry about me.
I've trained every last muscle in my body, so I'd be ready for anything.
Well, you obviously forgot the strength in your brain.
Yeah, you're right.
My brain's still pretty weak and flabby.
Hey!
That's not fair!
If there's a spell that makes a person smarter, can somebody cast it on Asta?
You're so thoughtful, you know!
Don't ask people to do stuff for me!
I'm sorry. I don't know one.
Oh, that's too bad.
Back to business.
The decisive battle is at hand, but you don't seem nervous at all.
What do we do if an enemy spy happens to find us out?
A spy, huh?
It's certainly a possibility, after all.
Think of the individuals who bribed the captain of the Purple Orcas and opened up the royal capital to attack.
No amount of caution would be unwarranted.
I guess not.
We'll be on guard.
Anyway, if all of us are headed into the capital, want a lift?
We'll take my vessel.
Are you sure you don't mind?
If you insist.
Yummy!
The food really is way better in the capital, huh?
Oops.
You silly.
There's some sauce on your face.
I'm so sorry.
That was far too presumptuous.
It's cool.
Thanks a lot.
Don't stuff your face.
You're supposed to be on alert, remember?
And you're definitely not supposed to be getting your face wiped by a...
I mean, not like I care.
Do whatever you want, stupid dorksta.
Look, I promise you guys, I'm totally on the ball.
I'm not pigging out.
I normally ain't twice this much.
Unbelievable.
I'm concerned.
It's not just Asta.
They may be talented, but some of the royal knights have... issues.
I can't wait to start fighting.
I'll pulverize those midnight sun guys till they're black and blue.
Zora's all by himself.
He's probably too shy to strike up a conversation.
Maybe I can bring him out of his shell.
Look what I can do.
Hey, I'm Zora Ideale.
Oh, no, Captain Rue.
Do none of you worms have any manners?
When you're eating a meal, you're supposed to enjoy it in the most graceful and beautiful fashion you possibly can.
Running away from my fork because you do not desire for me to consume you?
What a decidedly un-beautiful thing you are.
That's my brethren, you monster!
Ladies and gentlemen, it seems Pooley would like to entertain us with an original song.
I hate to be rude, but I'm filled with the urge to kill someone.
I'll never get any valuable intel as long as I'm stuck to him.
Nozel, what is it you'd like to discuss with me?
The fact that we're taking three days to set our plan into motion, isn't that too cautious?
What are you implying? Do you think I'm some kind of paranoid coward?
No. It appears that my reservations were unfounded.
Huh. Somebody's a fast learner.
I've set a trap to find out the extent to which the enemy knows our movements. Everything's under control.
Now then, I have a question too.
Did you really believe you could deceive me with such an insipid spell?
Oh, Dermot!
End of the line, Spy.
He's from the Eye of the Midnight Sun?
Wow. So they did have spies.
What a rotten trick!
Hey you, newbie. Apparently he chose you to be his conduit so he could tail us on our mission.
I can't believe I never noticed there was something amiss. What an absolute disgrace.
I've questioned this rodent within an inch of his life, and I've concluded that the enemy is not yet aware of our activities.
Therefore, I have moved up the date of departure, which means we storm their hideout first thing in the morning!
Wait! So soon?
But I thought we had three days!
No way! I don't want to let Yuno see what I look like as soon as I wake up!
I want everyone to be at their best, so get plenty of rest tonight. That is all.
If you ask me, it seems like Captain Mary Leona must have been planning from the very beginning for us to leave immediately if she caught an enemy sneaking around.
Well, they do say that to fool your enemies, sometimes you must begin by fooling your friends.
But still, we head out in the morning?
That Captain's really something else.
What's got you so upset, little fella? Are you starting to get scared?
It's the opposite. I want to become the Wizard King, so that I can bring peace and freedom to the Clover Kingdom.
I want everybody to smile.
They can't wreck our country. I won't let them!
Make sure you don't wreck our country by messing things up.
You won't get the best of me either, Yuno!
I'm going to win.
Well, here we go.
Right!
Tomorrow's the day. We'll finally put an end to all this.
The Royal Knights...
...will defeat the Eye of the Midnight Sun!
We'll be here for you.
Fire!
We're at the Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout.
There are few people who would venture into a strong magic area like this in the first place.
And with the added obscurity from that magical mist,
even those brave enough to seek it would have a hard time finding it.
Let me guess, that line of thinking was what helped you pinpoint the location,
wasn't it, Captain of the Silver Eagles?
I must say, I'm impressed.
The discovery was nothing but a stroke of luck, I'm afraid.
I was investigating a dungeon when I discovered the location of their hideout.
Really? And would you care to tell me your reasoning for coming out here with us?
Hmm?
There's hardly time for chit-chat.
Shirin, I believe your usual spell will work from here.
Of course.
Stone creation magic. Stone model of the world materialized.
Awesome!
Yes, I see. This place is structured like an anthill that we can enter from any angle.
It should be fairly easy to invade.
There are mages wielding senior level magic powers scattered throughout.
And someone more powerful in the larger center space.
I would assume that's their leader.
Yeah, that's licked. No doubt about it.
Nozel, sir, what is our battle strategy going to be?
I'm the captain of the Silver Eagles, not the Royal Knights.
That's a question for Mariliona.
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
Listen carefully!
The best way to beat them is to cause confusion with a surprise attack.
Usually, we'd enter separately to keep them from anticipating our moves.
But, having so many points of entry means the opponent is likely to be confident in their defenses.
The more spread out we are, the easier it will be for them to overpower us instead.
Which means, the most logical tactic is...
I know!
We just have to psych ourselves up so we can fight these guys even harder!
I can take care of them myself. No psyching up necessary.
I'll beat them senseless and crush their bones into powder!
I shall use my immaculate power to clear them out in one beautiful swoop!
Please just disappear.
I'm surrounded by morons.
Balance is key.
If the idea is to break up their numbers and still be able to overcome them,
then the best plan is to split into teams of four.
Don't you agree, Captain?
Wholeheartedly!
So we'll divide into five teams of four and make our move!
As long as I'm not stuck on the same team as this obnoxious Rugrat, I guess I'll be alright with anything.
Look, just because your mask is cool doesn't mean you get to be rude!
Plus, you're the obnoxious one around here!
Oh.
Then again, I don't think anybody's gonna want to work with you anyway,
so I guess I'll be a nice person and let you be a part of my team.
You'll change your tune when I save your weak ass from certain death.
You problem children are on my team. Behave yourselves.
At your service, Lady Royal.
In fact, I hope you'll accept this rainbow stink bug as a token of our acquaintance.
Don't do it!
Such a feeble odor isn't nearly enough to disarm me.
Great, but are you sure commoners like us would be fit to accompany a lady of your noble status?
Whoa, I didn't know you were a commoner just like me.
Whether a person is a royal or a commoner,
social status doesn't make the least bit of difference to me.
What does matter is whether you're strong or weak.
And you're both here because you're strong, are you not?
Two fools chosen by Yami.
I hope for your sakes you do not disappoint me.
Yes, ma'am!
Yeah, we'll do our best to come back in one piece. Is that good enough for you?
You should all be proud that you were selected to be our royal knights!
Now go use your skills to the fullest!
I've assigned your teams.
Team 1 will charge in from the upper left!
Yes, ma'am!
Of course!
Team 2, take the lower left!
Yes, ma'am!
Team 3, cover the upper right!
Team 4, take the lower right!
Yes, ma'am!
And we three members of Team 5 will attack them head on!
Ma'am!
Spatial Mage, remain on standby!
Absolutely, that won't be a problem at all!
Give it everything you've got, knights!
Here we go!
You foolish girl.
You do know how you got into this mess, don't you?
Well, the thing is, you're a resident of the Clover Kingdom.
And up until recently, that applied to me too.
But me, I was a bit different.
You see, I had my true name bestowed upon me by Master Ligt.
What I mean is, we're special, and you're not.
In other words, you're nothing but trash.
And so, we can treat you how we want.
That was way too easy.
They have stronger guys here, right?
I have some beautiful work to do, so try not to pick them all off on your own.
Are you alright?
I can't thank you enough.
A team like you shouldn't need a fully detailed battle plan.
Eliminate any who dare to get in your way as you head toward the center.
And of course, the method is up to you.
As long as you win, I couldn't care less how you do it.
The ants are coming out of the woodwork.
You've got some nerve.
Swooping in when I wasn't around.
And rampaging all over the royal capital.
You may have managed to escape from us during that encounter in the cave.
But this time is different.
Eye of the Midnight Sun.
This is the end for you.
You'll pay.
Right now.
This is for my rival.
This is for my brother.
We're going on!
Make no mistake!
Your leader's head will be mine!
Whoa!
Crazy!
I feel like she doesn't even need our help!
Apparently, we have a real tricky bunch on our hands.
Seeing as Licht isn't around.
This is going to be a pain.
Guess I'll have to suck it up.
I'm so sorry.
It's like a relationship if you wanted me to close your eyes.
This is the end for you.
It's hard for you to see as you get us.
Stay true!
I'm running back.
Bye.
Until next year.
!
Ah
So it takes us along with some white
I'm gonna be a little girl
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
I'll meet you again
Cloverclicks
Painful, Raya
Master Raya, Master Raya
Yeah, what are you so freaked out over?
Intruders
Seems that way, doesn't it?
But fighting them off would be a huge pain
So I'm just gonna stay here
Stay here, sir, we need you
Up is a pain though
Then I'll help you to your feet
Putting on my shoes is a pain
I'll take care of it
Standing's a pain too
Allow me
Walking's even more of a pain
Alright, forget it, I'm not going out
Really? Please reconsider, sir
I must have slept with my mouth open
Because my throat is feeling kinda scratchy now
Here's a sucker for you
What flavor is it?
It's apple?
This fight will be a pain
I guess I'll suck it up
What would have happened if it were orange flavored?
You know, I wonder how Vaultos and the others are doing right now
Black Clover
Page 89
The Black Bull's Hideout
Make sure you find what you're looking for, okay, Vaultie?
Oh, oh